It's like trying to fake the male orgasm.
And they'll probably do that, too.
Mm-hmm.
Perfect, perfect answer.
No, you were on The Five earlier,
and I'm surprised you didn't have that take on there.
I did.
They bleeped me.
I'm always getting censored.
But this is from the party that, you know,
when Pete Hexeth came out and said,
we have to have standards of physical fitness
in the military in order to be lethal and effective
and feared.
And it was the Democrats on MSNBC were like, oh my god,
that is so sizist and disgusting.
So you're telling me that you want
women to do difficult things in the military
in order to complete tasks so they can
compete on the global stage?
What is wrong with you, you monster?
And it's like demonizing physical fitness.
They're like, these poor generals.
So you're telling me you want the people who lead
the military to be able to do the physical fitness
standards that other people in the military
have to kill themselves trying to do?
What is wrong with you?
So it's like, you've already shown what you despise.
Right.
And you can't, it is so, to Brian's point
and his undescended testicle, it is so inauthentic
the next day to be like, oh my god,
I think going to the gym is great, right?
Like, I go here.
It's so natural.
It's almost like, Adam, he would understand this.
It's almost like a racist saying there,
oh, I love black people.
You get that.
Oh, all the time.
Look, I mean, to your point, I think everyone
should try to get in shape.
Like I'm on this new diet called Get Fatter Friends.
Where I just hang out.
But I do think that like, I don't get my politics
from a fitness influencer.
Just like I don't get my fitness from Chris Christie.
You know, and I think people should stay out of it
because I think it gets to be too much.
Pretty soon you're going to be watching a porn
and the guy in the middle of it is going to be like,
I'm getting an SGD right now, but that's okay
because Republicans are taking away my healthcare.
It's just like, but I do like that they're doing like guys
like Gavin Newsom are doing like this bro podcast
because it's exposing them.
Like he said, I'm a Swifty,
but I can't name one Taylor Swift song.
Which is like saying I use deodorant, but I'm French.